Today I would be talking about how to clip a horse.
The next thing that we would do is clip the underside of his jaw.
This is going to get his face just a nicer profile less of this shaggy look.
Again carefully turn the clippers on.
Make sure that your horse is comfortable with it.
I like to start right underneath his chin where the muzzle, where we are going to be working in the muzzle before and just slowly work my way up.
That could be hard when you horse is really hairy as he is to get a nice even look because the rest of his hair is so long.
We would get this really long stuff off.
It is important to make sure that we get both sides evenly.
So for this if you want to make sure we would cross over to the other side make sure that it is even.
That you have not missed any of these long hairs and you can see how ready he is getting a nicer profile.